{
    "id": "71f5c839988942128a73e5cf189d7066",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They ………………….. him hand and foot and  held him fast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bound",
                "bind",
                "binding"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cceabcf3df5642fd8aacad05e91b5d42"
        },
        {
            "question": "None of them …………………. of doing what he never attempted to do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dreamed",
                "dream",
                "dreaming"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1abb2a40e331419886a587668ad6600e"
        },
        {
            "question": "What he ………………….. he could not tell.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knew",
                "knows",
                "known"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b550971440714ef2b633cfd341f261f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "They .......................................... the roads so that he might not escape.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "guarded",
                "guard",
                "guarding"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f3f625fb6b464552bf538907520d4557"
        },
        {
            "question": "He came to my house to tell me what .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has happened",
                "had happened",
                "appear"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "58091e123c4346429193b5adc5e73a39"
        },
        {
            "question": "He promised that no one ............................................. for expressing their opinion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be persecuted",
                "would be persecuted",
                "would persecute"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "64335ef0449a4f6aae93ec6395df90ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "He got his shop .......................................... before the monsoons set in.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "repair",
                "repaired",
                "repairing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cb895650eb604787a37376170a2a8591"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ran so fast that he .............................................. soon out of breath.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8c6d183922724122bea5c14ef11dc601"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wonder what he has done with the money I .......................................... him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lend",
                "lent",
                "lending"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "54475ce349e64a16914b465b3db7c8ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ............................................... to you that he was simply bluffing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must occur",
                "must have occurred",
                "must occurred"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9739e148c9014738bb51db12fa01af5a"
        }
    ]
}